

CONTACT ME

- +351 960387787
- martimmauricio987@gmail.com
- Sesimbra, Portugal
- in Linkedin
- Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Beach Bar - O Horta 2024-2024

Bartender

- -Customer service;
- -Preparation and service of drinks;

La Villa Pizzeria 2023-2023

Waiter

- Order Management and Communication
- -Payment Processing;
- -Feedback and Complaints Management;
- -Collaboration with the Team;

SKILLS

- Java ¡Query
- Html SOAP
- CSS Maven
- SQL JavaScript
- OOP
- GIT
- JUnit

Martim Mauricio

Junior Fullstack Developer

ABOUT ME

<Hello everybody>

I just graduated from high school and recently completed the Fullstack bootcamp at Code for All_, where I learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, and React to build the internet!

I spent 8 years in Scouts and 9 years in catechism, where I learned teamwork, survival skills, and patience. Now, I'm ready to kick off my programming career, eager to learn and contribute every day.

If you're looking for a junior with energy, curiosity, and a positive attitude, let's chat!

EDUCATION

BootCamp Fullstack Code for All_ 2024-2024

High School Externato Gil Eanes 2023-2024

PROJECTS

 Game Jam Java: Rede Solidaria Java;

Html;

SQL; CSS:

JavaScript;

HOBBIES

- Travel;
- Video games;
- See series;
- Training;
- Gym;
- Sea;